nutcache.com 2016-12-02

# Privacy Policy - Nutcache

This Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use, disclosure and retention of the information provided by you as users of our Services or visitors of our Web site www.nutcache.com owned and controlled by Nutcache Technologies Inc. (“Nutcache”, “we”, “us”, “our”).

Nutcache Technologies Inc has been awarded Trust Guard’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by Trust Guard for compliance with Trust Guard’s program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The Trust Guard program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. Trust Guard’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at support@nutcache.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact Trust Guard. The Trust Guard certification covers information collected on our website.

Nutcache Technologies Inc has been awarded Trust Guard’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by Trust Guard for compliance with Trust Guard’s program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The Trust Guard program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. Trust Guard’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at support@nutcache.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact Trust Guard. The Trust Guard certification covers information collected on our website.

Nutcache complies with the Act respecting the Protection of personal information in the private sector (RSQ, c P-39.1).

Nutcache is committed to storing and processing your content and personal information on highly secured servers at OVH’s offices located in Beauharnois, Quebec and therefore is subjected to the laws and jurisdictions of Canada.

By using the Services, you are deemed to have read and understood the terms of this privacy policy. If you do not agree with the privacy policy, refrain from using the services. You can submit your questions pertaining to this Policy to our Privacy officer at [support@nutcache.com](mailto:support@nutcache.com).

## Effective Date

This Privacy Policy was last updated on February 22, 2013.

## Definitions

“Service” or “Services” or “Nutcache Services” shall mean the Nutcache.com Website, application and software offering functionalities of time, expenses and billing process management as well as any and all other services offered and available from time to time at Nutcache.com.

“Content” shall mean content such as data, text, images, contact information and links to content submitted to Nutcache.com as part of your use of the Service.

## Collecting Personal Information

In the course of providing the Services:

  * Nutcache collects personal information about you when you register with us. Said information can include, among others, your name, email address, and passwords, and other personal information (collectively, “Personal information”); Nutcache may also collect Identifiable Information from Visitors when they communicate with us about our Services or during interactions with our Users; Nutcache collects information about your clients so that you may set them up in the system. Information may include their name, email address, address, and phone number; We will collect information about your employees if you wish to add them to your account; we will collect their name, email address, phone number, date of birth and hire date; If you wish to create a new supplier we will ask for name, email address, address and phone number.

## Use of your Personal information

Nutcache will only use Personal information to:

  * Provide the Services you request; Time track by employee, process invoices, payments, expenses and run reports; Market Nutcache’s Services that may be of interest to you; and, Conform to request from authorities et legal obligations in accordance with the Act respecting the Protection of personal information in the private sector (RSQ, c P-39.1), and other applicable laws. Add clients to your account so that you may track time spent on them, create invoices, run reports, and bill them for services provided; Add employees to your account so that they may also track time spent on clients, create invoices, run reports and bill clients for services; Adding a supplier will allow you to contact that supplier when you need them to provide a service on your behalf. This information is only stored in our system so that you may use it to conduct business such as log a payment, process an order or invite them to use Nutcache.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter or marketing emails, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter or marketing to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe, you may do so by using the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at [privacy@nutcache.com](mailto:privacy@nutcache.com).

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Based upon the personal information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your email address. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account.

Nutcache will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service or sending out emails on our behalf. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

Nutcache may also use and disclose Personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, other legal process, to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activities that threaten the integrity of our Service or network, to investigate fraud or violations of our Terms of Service, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, your safety or the safety of others, or respond to a government request.

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

## Access and rectification

You can access, correct, delete inaccuracies, update, and rectify the Personal information we maintain by accessing your company settings and user profile or by emailing us at support@nutcache.com. We will respond to your access request within 30 days.

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at the email address listed above. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Other information collected

Nutcache and authorized third parties, may also collect and share with third parties, other information when you use our Services or visit our Website. Such information may include Internet browsing history, device used, demographic and location data, preferences and use of the Services.

## Log Files

As true of most Websites, we gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

## Cookies

The provision of the Services requires the placement of a cookie. A “Cookie” is an information file that may be placed on your computer by a Website for the purpose of facilitating and improving the use of our Services and Website. If you choose to block the placement of cookies you will not be able to use Nutcache’s services. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site.

In addition to cookies, Nutcache and third party advertisers may also use third party cookies to anonymously track and analyze online activity and use of our Services and provide specific advertising. You may block or restrict the placement of third party cookies, or delete them from your browser by adjusting your Internet browser settings or preferences. In such case, you may still use Nutcache’s services, but it may affect some of its functionality. The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

## Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ or our third party tracking utility partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

## Your Content

If you preserve the confidentiality of your access codes and/or passwords, and subject to the present policy, only you will have access to your Content and Personal information. People you share Content with will only see the parts you grant access to.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Nutcache has implemented the following security mechanism:

  * Information transmitted is securely encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software; Access control.

Nutcache will continue to revise its policies and implement additional security features as new technologies become available. However, no system or service can give a 100% guarantee of security, especially a service that relies upon a public network such as the Internet. Therefore, there remains a risk that third parties may gain unauthorized access to your information.

You must ensure the confidentiality of the access codes and/or passwords used to access your account. You are responsible for all activity occurring under your account(s) and shall abide by all applicable laws in connection with your use of the Service, including those related to data privacy, and personal information. You shall notify Nutcache immediately of any unauthorized use of any password or account or any other known or suspected breach of security.

## Links to Other Sites

This site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Website that collects personal information.

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this site.

## Public Forums

Our web site offers publicly accessible community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our community forum, contact us at privacy@nutcache.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Contact Us:

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us:

Nutcache Technologies Inc.

1270 Dagenais Blvd., West

Laval QC H7L 5E3

Canada

Email: support@nutcache.com
